poshdressup.com 2010-01-10

# Privacy | PoshDressUp.com

Search PoshDressUp 

Latest Posh Games [](http://www.poshdressup.com/games/fantasy-dressup/fantasea-dressup-1028.html) [](http://www.poshdressup.com/games/dressup-games/autumn-evening-dressup-871.html) [](http://www.poshdressup.com/games/dressup-games/prince-awesome-goes-medieval-827.html) [](http://www.poshdressup.com/games/dressup-games/colonial-girl-dressup-786.html) [](http://www.poshdressup.com/games/fantasy-dressup/galaedhel-the-elf-princess-721.html) Blog Categories  [Fashion](http://www.poshdressup.com/blog/category/fashion/) [News](http://www.poshdressup.com/blog/category/news/) [Celebrities](http://www.poshdressup.com/blog/category/celebrities/) [Gossip](http://www.poshdressup.com/blog/category/gossip/) [New Games](http://www.poshdressup.com/blog/category/new-games/) [Tips and Tricks](http://www.poshdressup.com/blog/category/tips-and-tricks/)

Latest Blog Posts 

[](http://www.poshdressup.com/blog/news/mtv-music-video-awards-2009/)Hey, Posh Girls! In today's article, we're raising the curtain on the long-awaited, red-carpet event of the fall: the MTV Music Awards which is set to take place on September, 13 at 9 p.m in New York. As the last year's edition, it will be hosted by Russell Brand and some famous live performers like Lady Gaga, Beyonce and hubby Jay-Z...[Read more](http://www.poshdressup.com/blog/?p=723 "Read more abour: MTV Music Video Awards 2009")

[](http://www.poshdressup.com/blog/celebrities/emily-osment-starts-her-music-career/) Emily Osment, the actress who portrays Lilly Truscott in the Disney Chanel hit TV series Hannah Montana has launched the first single on her debut album, entitled "All the Way Up" on Radio Disney. In addition, the video of the song has recently hit the market. As it appears, the 17-year-old actress followed the example given by her co-star...[Read more](http://www.poshdressup.com/blog/?p=718 "Read more abour: Emily Osment Starts Her Music Career")

[](http://www.poshdressup.com/blog/news/new-moon-official-trailer-no2/) The second installment of the Twilight saga, New Moon is set to be released in mid-November. However, you have currently the possibility to take a short glimpse at a second official trailer of this exciting vampire-flick featuring a beautiful love story between Bella (Kristen Stewart) and Edward (Robert Pattison) provided you are agog to see the p...[Read more](http://www.poshdressup.com/blog/?p=715 "Read more abour: New Moon Official Trailer No.2")

[](http://www.poshdressup.com/blog/gossip/ashley-green-and-chace-crawford-kiss/) Aside from rewarding talents from different fields of activity like music, sports, movie and providing you with a great show, unexpected surprises (what about the Jonas dares ? ) and your favorite celebrities, the Teen Choice Awards was also the perfect opportunity for a new couple to be unveiled. Reportedly, Chace Crawford, the Gossip Girl he...[Read more](http://www.poshdressup.com/blog/?p=708 "Read more abour: Ashley Green and Chace Crawford Kiss")

[](http://www.poshdressup.com/blog/news/spoiler-alert-teen-choice-awards-2009-winners/)The highly-anticipated summer event, Teen Choice Awards was held last night at the Gibson Amphitheatre in Universal City. As expected, it was star-studded and among the celebrities that hit the red carpet were the Black Eyed Peas, Gossip Girl's heartthrob Chace Crawford, Hayden Panettiere, Brenda Song, Britney Spears, Twilight cast members, Mile...[Read more](http://www.poshdressup.com/blog/?p=704 "Read more abour: Spoiler Alert: Teen Choice Awards 2009 Winners")

[](http://www.poshdressup.com/blog/celebrities/spoiler-alert-jordelle-ferland-casted-in-eclipse/)Even though it is set to be released only in 2010, the third sequel in the vampire-series, Eclipse has already made some headlines. Since the shootings are just at the beginning, most of the news focus on the cast of this movie which has pretty good chances of becoming a hit both at the Box-Office and among the fans given the gre...[Read more](http://www.poshdressup.com/blog/?p=700 "Read more abour: Spoiler Alert: Jordelle Ferland Casted in Eclipse")

[](http://www.poshdressup.com/blog/celebrities/taylor-swift-and-taylor-lautner-on-screen-kiss/) No, your eyes are not deceiving you! This picture which is not a fake portrays country-pop singer Taylor Swift locking lips with the also famous New Moon star, Taylor Lautner. However, their kiss is just a love scene shot on the set of a new romantic comedy, Valentine's Day, scheduled to be released on February, 2010. This ...[Read more](http://www.poshdressup.com/blog/?p=695 "Read more abour: Taylor Swift and Taylor Lautner On-Screen Kiss")

[](http://www.poshdressup.com/blog/celebrities/camille-belle-and-joe-jonas-broke-up/) Good news, Posh Girls! Joe Jonas is back on the dating market! According to multiple sources, the 19-year-old member of the Jonas Brothers pop-rock band and his girlfriend actress Camille Belle, have recently split up. Indeed, this is not just a swirling rumor, but an official news, as Belle's rep confirmed for various publications: ""Yes,...[Read more](http://www.poshdressup.com/blog/?p=690 "Read more abour: Camille Belle and Joe Jonas Broke Up")

Our Friends  [](http://www.bbdressup.com/) [](http://www.u-dress-up.com/) [](http://www.rainbowdressup.com/) [](http://www.girlgames4u.com/) [](http://www.smalldressup.com/) [](http://www.trendydressup.com/) [](http://www.kibagames.com/) [](http://www.flowerdressup.com/) [](http://www.iluvdressup.com/) [](http://www.gameland4girls.com/) [](http://www.roxigames.com/) [](http://www.enjoydressup.com/) [](http://www.difgames.com/) [](http://www.monigames.com/) [](http://www.dressupgirl.net/) [](http://theyellowfairybook.com/)

privacy 

The following is the official privacy policy for [www.PoshDressup.com](http://www.poshdressup.com/) , a website centered around flash games and child-friendly content. This Privacy Policy covers the issues related to personal information collected by the Site and information regarding tracking and information collection from our affiliates, advertisers and partners.

## Collection of Personal Information

At [www.PoshDressup.com](http://www.poshdressup.com/), we recognize that the privacy of your personal information is important and we take every measure to keep you informed on how we collect, safeguard and use your personal data, where applicable. We never sell your personal information to third parties, however our site might run scripts (such as Google Analytics) that collect log file information for analytical and statistical reports. The kind of information these third parties collect include your IP address, your ISP (Internet Service Provider), the browser you visit our site with (Firefox, Internet Explorer, Mozilla Firefox, Opera, Safari, etc), the pages you visit and the time you spend on pages of our site. This information is used strictly for ourselves, using it to better improve our site’s performance and user experience. We will never sell your personal information to third parties.

## Cookies and Web Beacons

Cookies are small text files that are placed in the visitor's computer with the purpose of storing their preferences. Cookies cannot damage user files, nor can they read information from a user's hard drive, they are purely "shortcuts" that allow web sites to remember users activities on a web site as well as users visits to a site. Since we use third party advertisements to support [www.PoshDressup.com](http://www.poshdressup.com/), there is a chance the companies running these ads might store your data in cookies, in order to collect advertisement information or protect you from abusive advertising (for example, stopping pop-up scripts from running multiple times from your IP). Because these advertisement companies may also collect the personal information stated above, we at [www.PoshDressup.com](http://www.poshdressup.com/) make sure we only use trustworthy 3rd parties, in order to protect our users.

In general, these cookies and web beacons are used for research purposes and for geo-targeting and behavioral targeting of the ads. If you feel uncomfortable providing this kind of information to our advertisers through cookies, you can turn them off from your preferred browser’s settings, or manage them through Internet Security software (such as Norton Internet Security for example).

## External Links

Our site has several external links pointing to our partners, or the flash games we post on our site might have in-game links to other sites that might offer content that we have no control over. Unfortunately, we cannot take responsibility for the content shown by our partners, although we only pick to link to related, quality websites that are non-intrusive and offer clean content suitable for our target audience.
